prohockeylife.com 2015-06-15

# Privacy Policy : Pro Hockey Life / Sports Rousseau / Entrepot du Hockey, The Ultimate Hockey Mega-Store

**Overview**  
Protecting your personal information is important to Pro Hockey Life Sporting Goods Inc., operating under the Pro Hockey Life, Sports Rousseau and L�Entrep�t du Hockey banners. To assure complete transparency, we have prepared this Privacy Policy (the �Policy�) to let you know how we will and will not use the information you entrust to us.

This Policy outlines the information PHL collects in connection with your registration, purchases and information requests made via PHL�s websites (prohockeylife.com, sportsrousseau.com and entrepotduhockey.com, hereinafter referred to as the �Site�), promotion/contest registrations, as well transactions carried out in our physical stores, and applies to PHL and its service providers.

**PRIVACY POLICY**

**WHAT INFORMATION DO WE ASK YOU TO SUBMIT?**  
In connection with registration, contests or purchases, we may ask you to submit your name, address, telephone number, email address, and other information.� In addition, in order to offer you an individualized online experience, we collect various types of information such as:  
\- domain names of visitors to our website;  
\- e-mail addresses of those who e-mail us;  
\- information on how many visits each page receives;  
\- information on what pages consumers visit; and  
\- information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.

**DO WE USE COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING MECHANISMS?**  
PHL uses cookies to remember information you gave us so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our website. Cookies are partially encrypted blocks of data that are placed on your computer and that are sent by your web browser to our computer when you visit this Site. The cookies that are placed on your computer have unlimited duration. If you delete or otherwise choose not to use cookies, you will still be able to use our Site, but you will need to re-select all preferences each time you return to our Site (such as language and country).�

**HOW WILL WE USE YOUR INFORMATION?**  
The personal information we collect allows PHL to:

\- process your registration; \- send you receipts for transactions carried out online or in our physical stores;  
\- improve our services, content and advertising;  
\- administer contests or similar promotions; and,  
\- keep you posted on PHL�s latest product announcements, promotions, and upcoming events.

PHL will not sell your personal information to any organization. Any third party users of the permissible list collected will adhere to the same privacy practices as PHL.

**SALE OR TRANSFER OF INFORMATION**  
In the event of a sale, merger, liquidation, dissolution, or sale or transfer of substantially all of the assets of PHL, all personal information collected about you from the Site may be sold, assigned, or transferred to the party acquiring all or substantially all of the equity or assets of PHL. Subject to your ability to opt-out as described below, you consent to the sale and transfer of your information as described in this paragraph.

**WHO HAS ACCESS TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**  
**Within Pro Hockey Life Sporting Goods Inc.**  
PHL restricts access to your personal information to our employees who need this information to serve you.

**Other Organizations**  
PHL, in some cases, uses industry leading service providers to facilitate customer service, delivery of orders and other key functions. We only share the information necessary for these service providers to perform their function. These third parties are strictly bound by confidentiality agreements to keep all customer information confidential.

**HOW WILL WE NOTIFY YOU IF THIS POLICY CHANGES?**  
PHL may update and/or revise this Policy at any time and will post the amended Policy on this Site. The amended Policy shall be effective upon posting, and your access to or use of the Site following an update shall be deemed consent to the revised Policy.

**OBTAINING YOUR CONSENT**  
By using the PHL websites, you are consenting to the collection and use of personal information provided by you to PHL, for the purposes and on the terms set out in this Policy.

**HOW TO OPT-OUT OR REQUEST CHANGES?**  
Should you wish to opt-out of receiving product announcements, promotions and communications relating to upcoming events, please send a request to�[privacy@prohockeylife.com](mailto:privacy@prohockeylife.com) or click the �unsubscribe� link on any communication you receive from us. Should an edit to your information be required, please advise us, and we will update your information in a timely manner.�
